[
  {
    "learning_path_id": "AZ204_02",
    "learning_path_name": "Implement Azure Functions",
    "learning_path_evaluation_items": [
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "001",
        "question": "What is a lifecycle management policy?",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": [
          "A lifecycle management policy is an array in JSON format containing between 1 and 100 defined rules."
        ]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "002",
        "question": "What are the four parameters of a rule as defined in a lifecycle management policy?",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": [
          "name: string",
          "enabled: boolean",
          "type: enum",
          "definition: object"
        ]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "003",
        "question": "What are the two items that each lifecycle management policy rule must include?",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": ["Filter set", "Action set"]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "004",
        "question": "What is the purpose of a filter set in a lifecycle management rule?",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": [
          "The filter set limits rule actions to a certain set of objects within a container or objects names."
        ]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "005",
        "question": "What is the purpose of an action set in a lifecycle management rule?",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": [
          "The action set applies the tier or delete actions to the filtered set of objects."
        ]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "006",
        "question": "True or False: If more than one filter is defined in a lifecycle management rule, a logical AND is used for evaluation.",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": ["True"]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "007",
        "question": "True or False: If more than one filter is defined in a lifecycle management rule, a logical OR is used for evaluation.",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": ["False"]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "008",
        "question": "True or False: If you define more than one action on the same blob, lifecycle management applies the least expensive action to the blob.",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": ["True"]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "009",
        "question": "True or False: If you define more than one action on the same blob, lifecycle management uses a logical AND for evaluation.",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": ["False"]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "010",
        "question": "True or False: If you define more than one action on the same blob, lifecycle management uses a logical OR for evaluation.",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/3-blob-storage-lifecycle-policies",
        "options": [],
        "answer": ["False"]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "011",
        "question": "What are three ways to add a blob-storage policy through the Azure portal?",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/4-add-policy-blob-storage",
        "options": [],
        "answer": [
          "Azure Portal List View",
          "Azure Portal Code View",
          "Azure CLI"
        ]
      },
      {
        "evaluation_item_id": "012",
        "question": "",
        "source": "https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/training/modules/manage-azure-blob-storage-lifecycle/5-rehydrate-blob-data",
        "options": [],
        "answer": [""]
      }
    ]
  }
]
